[
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'jaki' sounds like...",
    "answer": "yucky"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'jelo' sounds like...",
    "answer": "yellow"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'ken' sounds like...",
    "answer": "can"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'mani' sounds like...",
    "answer": "money"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'mi' sounds like...",
    "answer": "me"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'mun' sounds like...",
    "answer": "moon"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'tu' sounds like...",
    "answer": "two"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'wan' sounds like...",
    "answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'jan' sounds like...",
    "answer": "young"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'jo' sounds like...",
    "answer": "yo!"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'kama' sounds like...",
    "answer": "comma"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'lukin' sounds like...",
    "answer": "looking"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'pan' sounds like...",
    "answer": "pun"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'sama' sounds like...",
    "answer": "summer"
  },
  {
    "category": "0 - Spelling and Pronunciation",
    "question": "'sin' sounds like...",
    "answer": "seen"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "a",
    "question": "particle: (emotional interjection, emphasis or confirmation)"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "akesi",
    "question": "noun: lizard, reptile"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "ala",
    "question": "noun: nothing\nadjective: not, no, empty\nnumber: zero"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "alasa",
    "question": "verb: to hunt, to gather\nverb (unconventional): to search, to look for\npre-verb (unconventional): to try (doing something)"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "ale/ali",
    "question": "noun: everything, universe\nadjective: every, all, abundant\nnumber: all/infinite (simple system), 100 (complex system)"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "anpa",
    "question": "noun (old/non-pu): lower part\nadjective: bowing down, downward, lowly, humble, dependent\nverb w/o obj: to bow down\nverb w/ obj: to conquer, to defeat"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "ante",
    "question": "noun: difference, change, (unconventional) version\nadjective: different, other, changed\nverb: to change"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "anu",
    "question": "particle: or"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "awen",
    "question": "noun (unconventional): stability, safety, wait\nadjective: kept, safe, enduring, resilient, waiting, staying\nverb: keep, stay, endure, protect\npre-verb: continue (doing something)"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "e",
    "question": "particle: (specifies an object)"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "en",
    "question": "particle: and (combines subjects)"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "epiku",
    "question": "adjective: epic, awesome"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "esun",
    "question": "noun: trade, transaction, exchange\nadjective: trade/exchange-related, commercial\nverb: to trade, to exchange"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "ijo",
    "question": "noun: thing, object, matter\nadjective: material, physical"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "ike",
    "question": "noun: evil\nadjective: bad, evil, complex, unnecessary\nverb (unconventional): make smth worse"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "ilo",
    "question": "noun: tool, machine, device\nadjective: useful, (unconventional) electronic, metallic"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "insa",
    "question": "noun: insides, contents, center, stomach\nadjective: central, inside, between"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "jaki",
    "question": "noun: dirt, waste\nadjective: dirty, disgusting, toxic, unclean, unsanitary\nverb: to make something dirty"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "jan",
    "question": "noun: person, people, humanity, somebody\nadjective: human-like, personal"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "jasima",
    "question": "noun: mirror, reflection, echo\nadjective: opposite\nverb: to reflect, to reverse"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "jelo",
    "question": "noun/adjective: (the color) yellow (and its shades)\nverb: to color smth yellow"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "jo",
    "question": "noun: (unconventional) possessions, property\nverb: to have/carry/contain/hold"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "kala",
    "question": "noun: fish, marine animal, sea creature"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "kalama",
    "question": "noun: sound, noise\nadjective: loud, noisy, sound-making\nverb: to make noise, to recite, to play (an instrument)"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "kama",
    "question": "noun: event, arrival\nadjective: arriving, coming, future, summoned\npre-verb: to become, to be in the process of (doing smth), to manage to, to succeed in"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "kasi",
    "question": "noun: plant, grass, herb, leaf"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "ken",
    "question": "noun: ability, possibility, (unconventional) right, liberty\nadjective (unconventional): able, possible\npre-verb: can (do smth), may (do smth)"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "kepeken",
    "question": "noun: use, (unconventional) practice\nverb w/ obj: to use smth\npreposition: (do smth) using, with the help of"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "kijetesantakalu",
    "question": "noun: raccoon or other musteloid"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "kili",
    "question": "noun: fruit, vegetable, mushroom"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "kin",
    "question": "particle: very, really, also"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "kipisi",
    "question": "verb: to cut, to divide"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "kiwen",
    "question": "noun: hard object, metal, stone, solid\nadjective: hard, metallic, solid"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "ko",
    "question": "noun: powder, clay, paste, semi-solid"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "kokosila",
    "question": "verb: to speak not in toki pona in an environment where others speak toki pona"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "kon",
    "question": "noun: air, essence, spirit, (unconventional) gas\nadjective: invisible, ephemeral, (unconventional) gaseous"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "ku",
    "question": "noun: the Toki Pona Dictionary by Sonja Lang\nverb: to interact with ku"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "kule",
    "question": "noun: color, (rare) gender\nadjective: colorful, painted\nverb: to paint smth a color"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "kulupu",
    "question": "noun: group, community, company, society, nation, tribe\nadjective: communal, social"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "kute",
    "question": "noun: ear, hearing\nadjective: …-sounding\nverb: to hear, to listen, to obey"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "la",
    "question": "particle: “if/when” (introduces context)"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "lanpan",
    "question": "verb: to get, to take, to steal"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "lape",
    "question": "noun: sleep, rest\nadjective: sleeping, restful\nverb: to sleep, to rest"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "laso",
    "question": "noun/adjective: (the color) blue, green (and its shades)\nverb: to color something blue/green"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "lawa",
    "question": "noun: head, mind\nadjective: main, primary, controlling, ruling\nverb: to head, to control, to direct, to guide, to lead, to own, to rule"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "leko",
    "question": "noun: square, block, (sometimes) stairs"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "len",
    "question": "noun: cloth, clothes, fabric, layer of privacy\nadjective: clothed, made of cloth/fabric\nverb: to clothe, to provide a layer of privacy"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "lete",
    "question": "noun: cold\nadjective: cold, cool, raw, uncooked\nverb: to cool down"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "li",
    "question": "particle: (between subj. and verb/adj.)"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "lili",
    "question": "noun: smallness\nadjective: small, few, young\nverb: to shrink"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "linja",
    "question": "noun: long flexible object, string, rope, hair"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "lipu",
    "question": "noun: flat object, book, document, paper, page, record, website\nadjective: flat, used as lipu, lipu-like, of lipu"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "loje",
    "question": "noun/adjective: (the color) red (and its shades)\nverb: to color smth red"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "lon",
    "question": "noun: truth, life, existence\nadjective: real, true, present, existing\nverb w/o object: is true, exists\npreposition: in, at, on"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "luka",
    "question": "noun: hand, arm\nnumber: 5 (complex system)"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "lukin",
    "question": "noun: eye, vision\nadjective: …-looking, visual\nverb: to look, to see, to read\npre-verb: to seek (to do something)"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "lupa",
    "question": "noun: hole, door, orifice, window"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "ma",
    "question": "noun: earth, land, outdoors, territory, country"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "mama",
    "question": "noun: parent, ancestor, creator, origin, caretaker\nverb: to create, to parent, to take care of"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "mani",
    "question": "noun: money, large domesticated animal\nadjective: (unconventional) wealthy"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "meli",
    "question": "noun: woman, female, wife\nadjective: feminine"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "meso",
    "question": "noun: middle, center\nadjective: average, moderate, mediocre"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "mi",
    "question": "noun: i, me, we, us\nadjective: my, our"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "mije",
    "question": "noun: man, male, husband\nadjective: masculine"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "misikeke",
    "question": "noun: medicine, cure\nadjective: medicinal\nverb: to cure"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "moku",
    "question": "noun: food\nadjective: edible, of food\nverb: to eat, to drink, to swallow"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "moli",
    "question": "noun: death\nadjective: dead, dying\nverb: to kill"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "monsi",
    "question": "noun: back, behind, rear, butt\nadjective: back, rear"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "monsuta",
    "question": "noun: fear, monster\nadjective: scary, monstrous\nverb: to scare, to be afraid of, (sometimes) to turn into a monster"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "mu",
    "question": "(any animal sound)"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "mun",
    "question": "noun: moon, star, night sky object\nadjective: lunar, stellar"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "musi",
    "question": "noun: game, art\nadjective: entertaining, artistic, amusing\nverb: to amuse, to play, to have fun"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "mute",
    "question": "noun: quantity\nadjective: many, more\nnumber: 3 or more (simple system), 20 (complex system)"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "n",
    "question": "interjection: um…, hm… (“thinking noise”)"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "namako",
    "question": "noun: spice, addition\nadjective: additional, extra\nverb: to add, to spice up"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "nanpa",
    "question": "noun: number\nadjective: -th (ordinal indicator), mathematical, numeric, (unconventional) digital"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "nasa",
    "question": "adjective: weird, unusual, strange, drunk"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "nasin",
    "question": "noun: path, road, street, directive, way, custom\nadjective: street-, true to the directive/way/custom\nverb (unconventional): to guide, to show the path"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "nena",
    "question": "noun: hill, mountain, button, bump, nose\nadjective: hilly, mountainous, bumpy"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "ni",
    "question": "noun/adjective: this, that"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "nimi",
    "question": "noun: word, name"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "noka",
    "question": "noun: foot, leg, bottom, lower part, under (smth)"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "o",
    "question": "particle: (addressing people, commands)"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "oko",
    "question": "noun: eye"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "olin",
    "question": "noun: love, compassion, affection, respect\nadjective: loved, favorite, respected\nverb: to love, to respect"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "ona",
    "question": "noun: he, she, they, it\nadjective: his, her, their, its"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "open",
    "question": "noun: start, beginning\nadjective: initial, starting\nverb: to start, to open, to turn on\npre-verb: to begin (doing something)"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "pakala",
    "question": "noun: damage, mistake\nadjective: broken, wrong\nverb: to break, to make mistakes\nparticle: (generic curse)"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "pali",
    "question": "noun: work, labor\nadjective: working\nverb: to work (on), to make"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "palisa",
    "question": "noun: long solid object, branch, stick, (unconventional) length\nadjective: long"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "pan",
    "question": "noun: bread, grain, corn, rice, pizza"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "pana",
    "question": "adjective: (unconventional) given, sent, released\nverb: to give, to send, to emit, to release"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "pi",
    "question": "particle: “of” (regroups two or more modifiers)"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "pilin",
    "question": "noun: heart, feeling, touch, sense\nadjective: feeling, touch-based\nverb: to touch, to think, to feel"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "pimeja",
    "question": "noun: (the color) black (and its shades), shadow\nadjective: black, dark\nverb: to color smth black, to cast a shadow"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "pini",
    "question": "noun: end, finish\nadjective: final, completed, finished, past (with tenpo)\nverb: to end, to finish, to close\npre-verb: to end/stop doing something"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "pipi",
    "question": "noun: insect, bug"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "poka",
    "question": "noun: hip, side, nearby area\nadjective: neighboring, nearby, at one’s side"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "poki",
    "question": "noun: box, container, bowl, cup, drawer\nverb (unconventional): to put in a box"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "pona",
    "question": "noun: good, simplicity\nadjective: good, simple, friendly, peaceful\nverb: to improve, to fix"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "pu",
    "question": "noun: the official toki pona book\nadjective: as told in the official toki pona book\nverb: interacting with the official toki pona book"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "sama",
    "question": "noun: similarity, (someone’s) sibling\nadjective: similar, like, sibling\npreposition: as, like"
  },
  {
    "category": "5 - This and That",
    "answer": "seli",
    "question": "noun: heat, warmth, chemical reaction, heat source\nadjective: warm, hot\nverb: to heat"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "selo",
    "question": "noun: outer form, outer layer, shell, skin, boundary\nadjective: outer"
  },
  {
    "category": "7 - Interjections, Questions, Commands And Names",
    "answer": "seme",
    "question": "particle: what? which? (for questions)"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "sewi",
    "question": "noun: area above, top, highest part, sky, god\nadjective: high, above, divine, sacred"
  },
  {
    "category": "9 - Complex Adjectives and Contexts",
    "answer": "sijelo",
    "question": "noun: body, physical state, torso\nadjective: physical, of sijelo"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "sike",
    "question": "noun: circle, ball, cycle, wheel, (with tenpo) year\nadjective: round, circular, spherical, of one year\nverb: to make a circle around, to surround"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "sin",
    "question": "noun: novelty, addition, (unconventional) update, spice\nadjective: new, additional, fresh, extra\nverb: to add, to update"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "sina",
    "question": "noun: you\nadjective: your"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "sinpin",
    "question": "noun: face, foremost part, front, wall\nadjective: of face, foremost"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "sitelen",
    "question": "noun: symbol, image, writing\nadjective: symbolic, written, recorded\nverb: to write, to draw, to record"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "soko",
    "question": "noun: mushroom, fungus"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "sona",
    "question": "noun: knowledge, information\nadjective: known\nverb: to know\npre-verb: to know (how to do something)"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "soweli",
    "question": "noun: land mammal, animal"
  },
  {
    "category": "1 - Basic Sentences",
    "answer": "suli",
    "question": "noun: size, greatness\nadjective: big, heavy, tall, great, important, adult\nverb: to grow"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "suno",
    "question": "noun: sun, light, brightness, light source\nadjective: solar, bright\nverb: to light, to shine"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "supa",
    "question": "noun: horizontal surface"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "suwi",
    "question": "noun: (unconventional) sweets, fragrances\nadjective: sweet, fragrant, cute, adorable"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "tan",
    "question": "noun: cause, reason, origin\nadjective: original\nverb w/ object (unconventional): to cause\npreposition: from, because of"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "taso",
    "question": "particle (at beginning of sentence): but, however\nadjective: only"
  },
  {
    "category": "6 - Prepositions and Locations",
    "answer": "tawa",
    "question": "noun: movement\nadjective: moving\nverb: to move\npreposition: to, for, from perspective of"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "telo",
    "question": "noun/adjective: water, fluid, liquid\nadjective: wet, fluid, liquid\nverb: to water, to clean"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "tenpo",
    "question": "noun: time, moment, occasion\nadjective: temporal"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "toki",
    "question": "noun: speech, conversation, language\nadjective: verbal, conversational\nverb: to speak, to talk, to use language, to think"
  },
  {
    "category": "3 - Verbs and Objects",
    "answer": "tomo",
    "question": "noun: home, building, structure, indoor space, room\nadjective: indoor"
  },
  {
    "category": "13 - nimi ku suli",
    "answer": "tonsi",
    "question": "noun: non-binary person, trans person\nadjective: gender-nonconforming, trans"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "tu",
    "question": "number: 2\nnoun: divide\nadjective: divided\nverb: to divide"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "unpa",
    "question": "noun: sex\nadjective: sexual\nverb: to have sex with"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "uta",
    "question": "noun: mouth, lips\nadjective: oral"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "utala",
    "question": "noun: fight, battle, challenge, war\nadjective: aggressive, warlike\nverb: to fight, to battle, to challenge"
  },
  {
    "category": "8 - Colorful Language",
    "answer": "walo",
    "question": "noun: the color white (and its shades)\nadjective: white, bright/light\nverb: to color something white"
  },
  {
    "category": "11 - Numbers",
    "answer": "wan",
    "question": "number: 1\nnoun: part (of smth)\nadjective: united, married\nverb: to unite, to marry"
  },
  {
    "category": "4 - Oh No! More Vocabulary",
    "answer": "waso",
    "question": "noun: bird, flying creature"
  },
  {
    "category": "2 - Adjectives",
    "answer": "wawa",
    "question": "noun: strength, power, energy\nadjective: strong, powerful, energetic"
  },
  {
    "category": "12 - The Final Countdown",
    "answer": "weka",
    "question": "noun: absence, remoteness\nadjective: absent, away, remote\nverb: remove, get rid of"
  },
  {
    "category": "10 - Pre-verbs, Time and Place",
    "answer": "wile",
    "question": "noun: want, need, desire\nadjective: desired, needed, required\nverb: to want smth\npre-verb: to want to do smth"
  }
]